[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_v2",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_v2_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9206_Guardian",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_Armor_12_v2",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 40,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_v2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_title",
        "Description": "@0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0205_0102_Battles_Embrace_Gear_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_v2",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_v2_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9208_Shaman",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_Armor_11_v2",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 40,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_v2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Title",
        "Description": "@1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_v2",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_v2_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9207_Rogue",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "10_Quest_Armor_14_v2",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 40,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_v2_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1002_0104_Shrouded_Intent_Gear_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_lvl40_Weapon_v2",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_lvl40_Weapon_v2_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9201_Cleric",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_HopeManifest_00_v2",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 40,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_lvl40_Weapon_v2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_title",
        "Description": "@0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0203_0103_Hope_Manifest_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_v2",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_v2_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9202_Hunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_TheHuntress_00_v2",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 40,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_v2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Title",
        "Description": "@1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_v2",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_v2_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9203_FirePriest",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_FalmeasWrath_00_v2",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 40,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_v2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Title",
        "Description": "@1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0204_0104_Executioner_lvl40_Weapon_v2",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0204_0104_Executioner_lvl40_Weapon_v2_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9204_Executioner",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Executioner_00_v2",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 40,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0204_0104_Executioner_lvl40_Weapon_v2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0204_0104_Executioner_title",
        "Description": "@0204_0104_Executioner_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0204_0104_Executioner_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0204_0104_Executioner_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0204_0104_Executioner_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0204_0104_Executioner_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_v2",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_v2_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9205_Blademaster",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_KeenTemper_00_v2",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 40,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_v2_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "1hRShield_KeenTemperShieldT4",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1004_0103_Weapon_Keen_Temper_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
